Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Objects and Artifacts, 147716
  - Subseries A: General Objects and Artifacts, 147799
    - Geode fragment, undated; 147896 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0425)
      Description: Geode fragment--probably amethyst--purple in color
      Materials: geode--amethyst
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 4.5 x 4.25 inches
    - Rock with Crystal surface, undated; 147895 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0426)
      Description: Rock with top surface of crystal; orange and amber colors
      Materials: rock & crystal
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 3.5 x 2.5 inches
    - Paperweight, undated; 147894 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0427)
      Description: Paperweight shaped like faceted gemstone--aqua blue.
    - Paperweight, undated; 147893 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0428)
      Description: Oblong glass paperweight with clear opalescent coloring
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2.5 x 2 inches
    - Paperweight, undated; 147892 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0429)
      Description: Clear glass dome-shaped paperweight
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 3 inches
    - Paperweight, undated; 147891 (Box 135, Object 092.2.0430)
      Description: Green apple-shaped paperweight with bubbles in glass
      Dimensions: 2.25 x 3 inches
    - Birds Nest, undated; 147890 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0431)
      Description: Small bird's nest with two broken speckled eggs
      Materials: twigs, fiber, bird eggs
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 4 x 3.5 inches
    - Bird's Nest, undated; 147889 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0432)
      Description: Large bird's nest containing some dried flowers
      Materials: twigs, dried flowers
      Dimensions: 3.5 x 6 x 10 inches
    - Organic Twig Specimen, undated; 147888 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0433)
      Description: Twig with ?tree deformity or disease--balloon shaped twig with various holes throughout. Brown
      Materials: ?
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 3.5 x 1.5 inches
    - Insect Nest or Tree Deformity, undated; 147886 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0434)
      Description: Large cocoon-like shape. Light gray; numerous twig ends sticking out. Possibly diseased tree specimen or insect nest
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 3.25 x 2.5 inches
    - Bone and twig, undated; 147885 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0435)
      Description: Animal bone, possibly vertebra, with twig attached.
      Materials: Bone, twig
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 3.5 x 2.25 inches
    - Bone piece, undated.; 147884 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0436)
      Description: Long narrow piece of bone or cartilage with hole at top and wire loop hanging as pendant.
      Materials: bone or cartilage, wire
      Dimensions: 0.15 x 2.25 x 0.5 inches
    - Baby with crocodile Head, undated; 147883 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0437)
      Description: Plastic toy of crawling baby with movable hips, crocodile head attached. Painted brown.
      Dimensions: 6.25 x 3.25 x 8.25 inches
    - Crocodile, undated; 147882 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0438)
      Description: Crocodile toy with movable jaw; Green.
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2.25 x 6.75 inches
    - Lizard figurine, undated; 147881 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0439)
      Description: Standing Lizard toy with large wing-like shapes on sides of face & neck, long tail, open mouth, yellow and red
      Materials: plastic 8
      Dimensions: 5 x 5.5 inches
    - Wind up toy, lizard, undated; 147880 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0440)
      Description: Lizard toy with moving feet and wind up crank on left side. Green, yellow, orange, red.
      Where Made: "Made in Hong Kong" imprinted on bottom left foot
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 2.25 x 2.25 inches
    - Taxidermy--Frog, undated; 147879 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0441)
      Description: Preserved frog, open mouth. Brown
      Materials: Frog
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 4.5 x 6.5 inches
    - Taxidermy--Frog, undated; 147878 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0442)
      Description: Preserved frog standing on back legs holding percussion instrument (wooden guiro)
      Materials: Frog, wood, paint
      Dimensions: 6.75 x 3.75 x 2.75 inches
    - Insect Toy, undated; 147877 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0443)
      Description: Beatle with three horns and six legs. Winds up on bottom. Brown.
      Maker: "Tomy" imprinted on bottom side
      Where Made: "China" imprinted on bottom side
      Dimensions: 1.65 x 3.5 x 4.5 inches
    - Toy Insect, undated; 147876 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0444)
      Description: Six-legged insect, segmented back. Brown and yellow. Same as 092.0445 but different color.
      Dimensions: 1 x 2 x 2 inches
    - Toy Insect, undated; 147875 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0445)
      Description: Six-legged insect, segmented back. Black & gray.
      Materials: Plastic
    - Wind-up Toy crab, undated; 147874 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0446)
      Description: Crab toy with moving legs and eyes when would up. Red.
      Where Made: "Made in Hong Kong" imprinted on bottom
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 4.5 x 3 inches
    - Miniature dragon toy, undated; 147873 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0447)
      Description: Dragon with wings. Blue.
      Maker: "Russ" imprinted on bottom
      Where Made: "China" imprinted on bottom
      Materials: Rubber
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 1.5 x 2.25 inches
    - Toy Insect, undated; 147872 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0448)
      Description: Insect with wings. Black and green. Metal disk on bottom.
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 1.5 x 2.5 inches
    - Toy Insect, c.1983; 147871 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0449)
      Description: Insect with wings, legs, yellow eyes. Wheels on the underside.
      Maker: "Harty Toy Inc. no. 6000" Imprinted on bottom.
      Dimensions: 1 x 1.75 x 3 inches
    - Toy spider, undated; 147870 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0450)
      Description: Spider with eight black legs, yellow body, green eyes
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2.75 x 3.5 inches
    - Light set--Lizards, c. 1988; 147869 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0451)
      Description: "Bunch-a-Lizards" light set--contains 10 plastic gray and red lizards which fit onto a string of decorative lights.
      Maker: "Prinal Lite" printed on front and sides of box and "Sue Scott" printed lower right corner
      Where Made: Sticker on bottom states "Made in Taiwan"
      Materials: plastic, electric lights
      Dimensions: 1 x 6.5 x 3 inches
    - Firework, undated; 147868 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0452)
      Description: Firework with butterfly wings attached. Left wing printed in Chinese, right wing printed "Spring Butterflies (Large Size) Blue, red, orange, black.
      Maker: Top center printed with "Link Triad Brand" with logo
      Where Made: Bottom center printed "Made in Kwangsi, China"
      Materials: cardboard, fireworks
      Dimensions: 3 x 5.75 x 1.25 inches
    - Fly Toy, undated; 147867 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0453)
      Description: Fly with suction cup at mouth to mount on window. Green, black, red.
      Materials: plastic, paint, pipe cleaners
      Dimensions: 2 x 3.5 x 7.25 inches
    - Frog Acrobat, undated; 147866 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0454)
      Description: Toy made of wooden sticks with cardboard frog attached by string. Pressing bottom makes the frog flip over. In original but opened package.
      Maker: Sticker on package labeled "Club Earth"
      Where Made: sticker on package labeled "Made in China"
      Materials: wood, string, cardboard
      Dimensions: 9.15 x 2.15 x 2.25 inches
    - Alligator Figurine, undated; 147865 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0455)
      Description: Alligator with open mouth, gray
      Maker: Mark on underside of alligator--undetermined
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2.5 x 8.5 inches
    - Stone in box, undated; 147864 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0456)
      Description: "Crocodile Scute" --flat stone with holes or gouges. In box with card identifying it as "crocodile scute"
      Materials: stone; box--cardboard, cotton, paper, ink
    - Crystal, undated; 147863 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0457)
      Description: Piece of crystal, possibly amethyst. White and purple.
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2 x 1 inches
    - Pin, undated; 147862 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0458)
      Description: Stick pin with circular image of male saint w/child--probably Joseph and baby Jesus.
      Materials: metal, image
      Dimensions: 1.65 x 0.75 x inches
    - Crystal pendant, undated (Box 133, Object 092.2.0459)
    - Crystal Pendant, undated; 147861 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0460)
      Description: Clear tear drop shaped pendant hung on a multi-colored thread braid with clear bead at top. Red, yellow, green.
      Materials: crystal, thread.
      Dimensions: 6.5 x 0.5inches
    - Double Sided Lithograph, undated; 147860 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0461)
      Description: Double sided lithograph
      Maker: No signature
      Materials: lithograph
      Dimensions: 24 x 35inches
    - Original study of pint, 1990/1991; 147859 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0462)
      Description: Multimedia collage with swastika in a sun, the grim reaper ('democracy at work") descending upon people with voice bubbles "saying" things like "starvation" & "homophobia"
      Maker: signature on center right bottom of piece
      Materials: oil stick, collage, press type
      Dimensions: 23 x 20inches
    - Psychiatric Clinic: Court of Benjamin Sessions, June 1, 1983; 147858 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0463)
      Description: Paint and Ink. Red Blood-like blotch over images of people walking and standing.
      Maker: David Wojnarowicz and Kiki Smith on bottom right hand corner below title
      Materials: Ink, Paint
      Dimensions: 17.5 x 22.5inches
    - Stencil, undated; 147857 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0464)
      Description: Stencil of Flames
    - Text Poster, 1985; 147856 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0465)
      Description: Poster--Black & White photo of man on left, text on right with red square image of 2 figures beating a third figure on the ground
      Maker: No signature, but printed on right hand side and between C & D printed along right hand side (cont)
      Materials: printed poster
      Dimensions: 16 x 22inches
    - Romulus and Remus Screen-print, 1983; 147855 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0466)
      Description: Screenprint--2 pieces of paper. Wolf with earth on back. Two babies suckling and the burning house stencil in his middle
      Maker: signed. Bottom left hand of image
      Materials: stencil
      Dimensions: 23 x 3inches
    - Kondoleon Poster, signed with date 1989; 147854 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0467)
      Description: Poster for theater for the New City. Images of Grim Reaper, train emerging from brain, and 2 figures with gun
      Maker: signed bottom center
      Materials: collage, water color paint, ink
    - Hunger, 1981; 147853 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0468)
      Description: Stencil print "Southern /Jumbo / Yams..." Green stencil, silver stencil of knife, plate, fork on top of green. Soldier, syringe.
      Maker: bottom left hand side, and (?) on right hand side
      Materials: stencil, spray-paint
      Dimensions: 22 x 34inches
    - Early Stencil 1, undated; 147852 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0469)
      Description: Stencil of gorilla with arms tied to posts.
      Maker: no signature
      Dimensions: 21 x 22inches
    - Early Band Poster 2, 1980-81; 147851 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0470)
      Description: silkscreen, "3 Teens Kill 4" Pyramid Ave A 6 & 7th st. Thurs Jan 21. In blue below green soldier running over red brick
      Maker: lower right corner
      Materials: spray-paint stencil 17.5
      Dimensions: 14 x 0inches
    - Panda Stuffed Animal, Undated; 092.2.0471; 147850; 1 item one stuffed animal (Box 092.2.0471)
      Description: Panda stuffed animal
      Maker: n/a
      Where Made: n/a
      Materials: fabric, stuffing
      Dimensions: 22 x 15.5 x 9.5 inches
      soft toys
    - Plastic clown head, undated; 092.2.0472; 147849; 1 item one toy (Box 092.2.0472)
      Description: plastic clown head, blue hat, grinning mouth, red nose, yellow and red polka dot tie.
      Dimensions: 17 x 10 x 11 inches
      Toys.
    - Clown Toy, Undated; 147848; 1 item one toy (Box 138, Object 092.2.0473)
      Description: Push button swinging clown toy
      Materials: plastic and paint
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 3 x 1.5 inches
    - Bull Skull, undated; 092.2.0474; 147847; 1 item one skull (Item 092.2.0474)
      Description: Bull Skull
      Materials: cow skull
      Dimensions: 5 x 17 x 11 inches
      skulls (skeleton components)
    - Skull rock and chain, undated; 092.2.0475; 147846; 1 item one rock with chain attached (Box 141, Object 092.2.0475)
      Description: round piece of rock (cement?) in shape of skull attached to a metal chain.
      Materials: rock, metal
      Dimensions: 9 x 38 x 12 inches
    - Beer keg, undated; 092.2.0476; 147845; 1 item one can (Box 145, Object 092.2.0476)
      Description: Mini beer keg. "Lowenbrau Zurich" has round holes and collapsed, rusty top and bottom
      Materials: tin
      Dimensions: 9.5 x 7 x 7 inches
      Cans (containers)
    - Large bull skull, undated; 092.2.0477; 147844; 1 item one skull with hanging fixtures on horns and lower jaw (Box 092.2.0477)
      Description: Large bull skull with hanging fixtures on horns and lower jaw
      Materials: skull, bone
      Dimensions: 16 x 20 x 20 inches
    - Wooden block, undated; 147843 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0478)
      Description: Toy wooden block with the letter P on one side. Image of a plane on another. The Letter H and image of a bird
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 1.75 x 1.75 inches
    - Watch, undated; 147842 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0479)
      Description: wrist watch with yellow face
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 1.25 x 4 inches
    - Beaded Band, undated; 147841 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0480)
      Description: Beaded band with white, blue, orange, purple, gold and green beads
      Materials: beads, string
      Dimensions: 1 x 17 inches
    - Flying beetle necklace in green box, undated; 147840 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0481)
      Description: Silver necklace. Scarab beetle with wings, 2 green stones and 2 white beads and chain
      Materials: silver, beads
      Dimensions: 12 x 1.5 inches
    - Oil drill coin purse, undated; 147839 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0482)
      Description: coin purse with side zipper and image of oil drill
      Maker: c. MAFCO on bottom left (which zips to left hand side)
      Materials: cloth, ink
      Dimensions: 4 x 3 inches
    - Bag of pink marbles, undated; 147838 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0483)
      Description: Plastic fishnet bag of pearly pink marbles
      Materials: pearly pink marbles in fishnet plastic sack
      Dimensions: 6 x 3 x 3 inches
    - Fingernail clipper with camouflage top, undated; 147837 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0485)
      Description: Small fingernail clipper/knife/can opener with camouflage plate as top
      Materials: metal, plastic
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 2.5 x 0.5 inches
    - Yellow beads in plastic bag, undated; 147836 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0484)
      Description: Plastic beads in clear bag with price on outside
      Materials: yellow beads in fishing wire inside plastic bag
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 3 x 0.5 inches
    - Tin Heart Ornament, undated; 147835 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0486)
      Description: Tin ornament with a heart on the center, designs surrounding the heart, and sharp pointed edges. "GR" engraved in center with dots.
      Materials: Tin
      Dimensions: 3 x 2.25 inches
    - Bag of mixed color beads, undated; 147834 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0487)
      Description: Multi-colored beads in a plastic bag. Nylon bead card also included.
      Materials: beads (red, orange, green, white); nylon cord; plastic bag
      Dimensions: 5.34 x 3 x 25 inches
    - Stamp flag and bag of stamps, undated; 147833 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0488)
      Description: Waxed paper bag of loose 25 cent and one 25 cent with $ written on it, attached to blue stir stick.
      Materials: USPS stamps (25 cent), tape, stirring stick
      Dimensions: 2 x 4.25 inches
    - Dog tags on chain, 1990; 147832 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0489)
      Description: One dog tag reads "Oh I want to Farm that blowboy" and the other "David Wojnarowicz 1990"
      Maker: Dog tag
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2 x 0.25 inches
    - Blue snake tail string, undated; 147831 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0490)
      Description: String of large blue beads and snake tail at bottom. Blue piece at top reads "poison".
      Materials: glass, rattle snake tail
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 0.5 inches
    - American Flag stitched to banner "Lionel", undated; 147830 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0491)
      Description: Stitched American flag sewn to string and to banner
      Materials: cloth, string
      Dimensions: 16 x 3 inches
    - Clock face, 4/17/1995; 147829 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0492)
      Description: Metal clock face
      Dimensions: 2 x 2 inches
    - Pipe, undated; 147828 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0493)
      Description: Plastic pipe, wood-look, carved sides, "medico" on side
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 5 x 1.5 inches
    - Copper Pierced Heart Ornament, undated; 147827 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0494)
      Description: Copper heart, engraved with patterns, pierced by arrow, string tied around top.
      Materials: copper, string
      Dimensions: 35 x 3 inches
    - Charms "B" and Gold Bead Chain, undated; 147826 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0495)
      Description: Assorted metal charms including skull, "Roma," and more. Gold beaded chain.
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 0.5 inches
    - 2 Ring, undated; 147825 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0496)
      Description: 2 rings, one gold in color, the other silver with blue
      Dimensions: 1 x 1 x 5 inches
    - Spinning globe trinket, undated; 147824 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0497)
      Description: metal spinning globe with ring on top. Continents marked by name.
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 1.5 x 1 inches
    - Larger Trinkets, undated; 147823 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0498)
      Description: "1. Green splotchy smooth stone2. Clear ball pendant with ""seed"" inside.3. Green plastic clump4.Frog pin5.""Gold"" lock"
      Materials: plastic, stone, metal
    - Clock Face, undated; 147822 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0499)
      Description: Metal clock face; white w/ black lettering
      Maker: -----
      Where Made: ------
    - "Daxaca" Pin, undated; 147821 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0500)
      Description: Metal pin of human figure dancing & wearing a large hat. Brightly colored.
      Maker: ----
      Where Made: ----
      Dimensions: 4 x 1.5 x inches
    - Turtle Pendant, undated; 147820 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0501)
      Description: Marble-esque pendant "925" engraved on turtle's harness--on belly
      Maker: ---
      Where Made: ---
      Materials: marble?, metal1.5.5
    - 4 Blue Beads, undated; 147819 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0502)
      Description: 4 blue beads in plastic bag
      Materials: ceramic (?)
      Dimensions: 0.15 x 0.15 x 0.15 inches
    - Small stone Head, undated; 147818 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0503)
      Description: Green and white head with chunks missing.
      Materials: stone?
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 0.5 x 0.5 inches
    - Charms "A", undated; 147817 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0504)
      Description: Assorted Metal Charms
    - Fabric Stick in Glass Jar, undated; 147816 (Box 132, Object 092.2.0505)
      Description: Fabric covered stick in glass mason jar
      Materials: glass, fabric
      Dimensions: 9.5 x 5 x 5 inches
    - Multi-colored Beetle in Plastic Box, undated; 147815 (Box 132, Object 092.2.0506)
      Description: Green and orange beetle. "Eudicella Grall: Hubin." In plastic box.
      Materials: Beetle, pins, foam board, plastic box
      Dimensions: 2 x 2.5 x 3.5 inches
    - Scorpion in Green Diamond-cube, undated; 147814 (Box 132, Object 092.2.0507)
      Description: Green "diamond-cube" with dried (real) scorpion inside
      Materials: plastic, scorpion
      Dimensions: 3 x 7 x 7 inches
    - Red Shawl, undated; 147813 (Box 132, Object 092.2.0508)
      Description: Red-fabric shawl with darker red designs
      Materials: cloth
      Dimensions: 33 x 77 inches
    - Two and a half horseshoes, Undated; 147812; 3 items two horseshoes and one half of a horseshoe (Box 138, Object 092.2.0531)
      Description: 2 full horseshoes and a half a horseshoe
      Materials: Iron, horseshoes?
      Dimensions: 4 x 5inches
      Horseshoes (animal equipment)
    - Horseshoe magnet set, Undated; 147811; 1 item one package of horseshoe-shaped magnets (Box 137, Object 092.2.0532)
      Description: Packages of horseshoe magnets
      Materials: plastic, magnet, metal, paper
      Dimensions: 8 x 5.5 x 0.25 inches
      Magnets.
    - Pavement chip, Undated; 147810; 1 item one piece of pavement (Box 138, Object 092.2.0533)
      Description: Piece of pavement chip with black paint, round circle in white "1:12" written in pencil
      Materials: Pavement, paint, pencil
      Dimensions: 4.5 x 4.75 x 0.15 inches
      Pavements (surface elements)
    - Bag of syringes & adrenaline, Undated; 147809; 1 item one plastic bag with syringes and adrenaline (Box 138, Object 092.2.0534)
      Description: Plastic bag of syringes and adrenaline.
      Materials: syringes, adrenaline chloride solution
      Dimensions: 9 x 5 x 1.5 inches
    - Money House 1, undated; MSS.092.2.0535; 147808; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object MSS.092.2.0535)
      Description: 1 of three houses--largest--All nest together. Originally shown at P.P.O.W date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
      Materials: cardboard, paper
      Dimensions: 17.25 x 14 x 16.75 inches
      Props (object genres)
    - Money House 2, undated; MSS.092.2.0536; 147807; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object MSS.092.2.0536)
      Description: 1 pf 3 houses-medium-- All nest together. Originally shown at P.P.O.W, date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
      Dimensions: 12 x 11 x 12 inches
    - Money House 3, undated; MSS.092.2.0537; 147806; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object MSS.092.2.0537)
      Description: 1 of 3 houses--all nest together--originally shown at P.P.O.W., date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
    - Small Monkey Skull, undated; 147805 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0538)
      Description: Small monkey skull with "#413" written in pencil on bottom
      Materials: skull
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 2 x 4.5 inches
    - Stuffed Reptile, undated; 092.2.0541; 147802; 1 item one taxidermied reptile (Box 092.2.0541)
      Description: Bleached stuffed alligator. Front legs tied to each other with rope. Back legs tied together with rope. Visible stuff line along the bottom (belly area) and visible stuffing)
      Materials: alligator, rope, stuffing
      Dimensions: 2 x 7.5 x 35 inches
      Taxidermy mounts.
    - Cow skull, undated; 092.2.0542; 147801; 1 item one skull (Box 092.2.0542)
      Description: Cow skull found in the desert with worm casings
      Materials: cow skull, worm casings
      Dimensions: 7 x 8 x 18 inches
    - Wolf's head, Undated; 147800; 1 item one sculpture (Box 092.2.0543)
      Description: Papier-mache mask in shape of wolf's head. Head made of New York City newspapers with AIDS-related headlines visible. Edge of mouth, inside of ears, and edges of eye holes painted red. Teeth made of cardboard, painted white. Mouth is open, large red-painted papier-mache tongue visible.
      Materials: Materials/medium description papier mache, corrugated cardboard, masking tape, paint
      Dimensions: 26 x 19 x 14 inches
  - Subseries B: The "Magic Box", 147739
    - Magic Box, undated; 092.2.0543; 147798 (Box 092.2.0543)
      Description: Wooden box with sliding lid painted in orange and green: Indian River Citrus on top and Florida's Finest Citrus on the front and back. Strip of masking tape on top with Magic Box written in marker.
      Maker: Title Magic Box is in Wojnarowicz's handwriting.